Yes, ma'am.
I'd like to go and have a look at it.
Yes, sir.
Shall we do this?
Thank you very much.
Shall we go?
Shall we?
Live Broadcast
Let's go.
Oh, oh, oh, Mr. Cho.
I'd like to hear a little more from the gut.
That's very tough. Let's go for the live feed!
Let's do it! Please do.
Ah! Aah! Aah!
Aah!
I've been hiding from you.
I've been hiding.
Now I've been exposed.
It's been six months since I've had those dumpling buns.
It's been six months.
It's my first shift.
Maybe there was a problem.
Maybe there was a problem, and he wasn't here, and now he's finished with the miso soup.
There's no problem at all.
Not at all.
On the coffee shop's side.
They just forgot to put in their shift.
They forgot to serve it. They forgot to serve it.
That's so true. Before that, there were a lot of gyoza buns coming in.
So, since they stopped coming all of a sudden, there's definitely something going on.
No, it wasn't! No, it wasn't!
But if they make a scandal about dumpling buns, we'll laugh. What kind of scandal?
What would it be?
It's a little hard to imagine.
Aggravating... Aggravating...
Well, that's why I'd like to continue this week's report in a loose, loose manner.
First of all, I'd like to tell you about the recordings. Today is the 9th or 10th of January. First of all, let's start with the recording, which is today, the 9th or 10th of January.
The recording will take place on the 26th of January, so that's how I'd like to start.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, sir.
So that's how it is.
It's the 26th of January.
That's early.
But I somehow realized that it's already the second half of January, right?
No, it's true.
Hey, January.
Januaries.
Januaries soon.
Januaries will be over?
Oh, no.
Hey.
February goes by so fast.
That's right.
But this year is the year of Uru.
That means...
Oh, why, it's until the 29th.
Oh!
The Olympic year is until 29, right?
I see.
What's an Olympic year?
It's the year of Uru.
Wow!
I see.
Then of course there is the Olympics.
The year of Uru.
So, a person born on February 29th will continue to age normally, but he/she can only have a birthday once every four years, right?
Not just not possible, but official.
It's not that they can't have a birthday, but they can't have an official birthday.
I know one person who was born on February 29.
Wow, that's great.
There is Kiyoe-chan, who is in charge of living things.
Wasn't she born on February 29th? I believe Kiyoe was born on February 29, wasn't she?
That's right.
Wow, that's amazing.
Is this a fake?
Gase?
I wonder which one it is.
I think it's written in "uru".
Yes, that's right.
That's right. It seems so.
If you see it, it's from you. Yes, it is.
If you contact me, I'd love to hear from you. I don't know him, though.
Mizuno-kun would be fine. Mizuno-kun, how are you, really?
I haven't heard a peep out of you lately.
Yes, yes, yes. So, it's the 26th of January, which is, you know, a little bit, you know, exactly...
It's a day for pay parking, a day for parking meters.
In 1959, Tokyo's Hibiya-Marunouchi area
In the Hibiya-Marunouchi area of Tokyo, the first so-called coin-operated parking lots, or street parking lots, were built.
I don't think it was automatic like today.
1283 parking meters were installed.
Amazing! Commemorative
The first one was installed in Yurakucho
10 yen per 15 minutes.
Well, well, well... monetary value was different.
At that time, you could buy a piece of tofu or a postcard for 10 yen.
That's cheap. You can't buy a tofu now.
Not even close. On a day when you parked for 15 minutes...
You must have been very conscientious.
Starting salary for a college graduate was 15200 yen back then
I guess it's like that... 15 years old and now, 15, 20. That's about right. I see.
No, no, no. It's a parking day.
Well, you know, in 2024, one thing I would like to push for, in a very devilish way, is a heroic story.
Yes, that's right. Yes, that's true.
It seems that there are heroes.
Yes, there are.
It seems like they exist.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. No, it's not.
Are you there?
You haven't seen him?
We have met.
Yes, I did.
I came, didn't I?
How was it?
I don't know. I flew, but I didn't move at the same time.
I flew.
That's too much to ask, isn't it?
No, no, no, no. That's why he just flew away.
You didn't mean to disappear.
You didn't intend to disappear.
I think he's a bit of a dumb hero.
And, you know, Kalimenraiya.
I'm not sure what to call him, but he was the original master of the Kamen Rider, right?
The name of Dr. Fujioka, who was an early rider of the Kamen Rider series, is a famous quote from him.
I have drawn a picture of Dr. Fujioka, who did the first 8 Masked Riders, but the balance is not quite right.
I'm going to make this girl, but she's got a big head and a lot of hair, so I started with her hair.
I started with her hair, and then I thought her face was too small.
I bought it at this level. Well, Mr. Fujioka has a lot of hair, so I had to have a lot of hair.
Then I ended up with this... Dr. Fujioka, you look like Hirose.
This man worked on the first Kamen Rider, the true legend.
The person who sent this to us would like you to come and read it.
Dr. Fujioka said he'd like you to read it.
No rehearsal, no encore...
My hair! Cut it!
I see... No encores.
It's always a live performance. There's no encore.
To! He flew away.
I'm so cool! So, I've received a letter from you... about the Masked Rider.
We also received a letter from Mr. Dancing Nippon Everybody, Arakawa Ward, Tokyo.
This person found out about the Masked Rider project and cosplayed as soon as possible!
He is the first one to cosplay as Masked Rider! The first cosplayer! It's amazing!
It's amazing. Which one shall we start with? Maybe...
Is this one good? Is that good? Yes!
Yes!
I like it! I love it!
I knew you had the right hands on point!
Nice back muscles! That's great!
I want to play with him!
This one looks much more like a rider. Yes, it's green.
And the belt looks like a transformation belt. It's cool. It looks cool.
According to Nippoli, he did it before he saw the Rider at the end of the year when he was on duty in his homeland.
He said he did it with that image. Is there a link between the image and this place?
Amazing! Amazing!
Amazing! And the poses...
Like a transformation pose. This is a transformation pose, or an enthusiastic pose.
Enthusiastic!
Wow! Looks like fun.
It's true that they're doing it on a rooftop or something, but it really looks like it.
That's amazing.
Thank you so much!
I love it.
And another photo. What's this one for?
Oh, it's a handshake! He's asking for a handshake of friendship.
I love it!
He's a hero for peace.
Wow! That's funny.
I don't think I've ever seen him before. How about you?
I like it, it's great, but his hands are...
They're very distinctive, but with a more perverted look.
Perverted, yes.
It's like the opening vid of Ryan's movie, right?
I saw it. I watched it.
Who's that weird guy in the back?
Is that him? He was doing this.
I think it's after he saved someone.
After he helped someone in trouble on the street.
He gave us a ride.
Maybe he was the victim.
That's right.
I'm thinking about it. Can you carry him? I'm thinking of it. Can you carry it?
Yes. It's inspired by Ultraman Cosmos.
I'll give it back to you.
I see. Usually, a hero is a hero once he's defeated Ako.
Yes, until he takes it.
He'll take you home.
He's going to take you home?
Maybe the masked liar will.
That's cool.
Well, then... he's in a good mood.
He was drunk and asked for a ride.
And then he's in a hurry to pawn it.
He was pawning?
Like a cab.
I've lost my training.
Hey, Masked Liar, you wanna go right now?
There might be a line.
But he might come dressed like that.
Well, well, well... that's all possible.
I see.
Also...
If I was walking down the street...
I was walking down the street.
I saw that flower bed.
Flower beds?
The so-called...
I don't know what to call it.
On the side of the road.
The locals take care of them.
on the side of the road
Everyone walks right in front of it.
Is this Nakano?
No, it's not.
It's here.
It's a two-choice book.
It's just that most flower beds talk about the same thing.
Well, well, well, you're right. Well, well, well.
I'll take that one.
After this.
I want you to take care of the flowers.
There were a lot of signs made by local children, or maybe students.
There were many signs made by local children, or maybe students.
But there was one sign among them... that I really wanted Gyoza Pan to read.
I really want Gyoza-pan to read it.
It looks like this.
No, no, no!
Don't ruin the show. I like it.
Isn't this nostalgic? It's a gag from the Heisei era. I think it won the "buzzword of the year" award.
That's right, Akimi.
I think it was made in that era.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I think it was made in that era. I hope they'll make a voice version.
I really want it to have a voice.
I said, "I like it," but it's gotten interesting over time.
I said, "I like it," but it's gotten old and it's interesting.
It's in Kanagawa, so the turtle is the character, like Kamekichi-kun.
Like a turtle statue. A turtle character.
Can I try one more time? No, no, no...?
I like the 2021 version. It's full of material.
When you're walking along the street, there are interesting signs.
You don't expect to find things like roadside deities and small Jizo statues, do you?
Yes, there are. I've been worshipping them a lot lately.
There is a god who is usually enshrined in a shrine like this.
This is a very wonderful god.
It's kind of cool, isn't it?
I'm playing the original, so...
He's got a nice face.
He looks happy.
I think this type of god is "Tojiten".
I like it.
Nice work. Looks like fun.
I'm like this too, so when I play guitar, I'll be like this.
It's true. It might become automatic.
I'm petrified. I feel petrified.
Well, well, well, well, well, well... Well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
May I make an announcement?
First of all, we have VIP seats.
Yes, there's a little more...
VIP! VIP!
When I was young, I couldn't get in the VIP section of a disco.
You couldn't? You can't go in there with a dress code like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is this what I look like?
No, I can't go in there.
You're a little well put-together, aren't you?
Yes, it is.
We'll be accepting applications until 11:59 p.m. on Sunday, January 14.
This is a great opportunity.
You have to buy a ticket, right?
You have to buy a ticket.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like that.
It's fun.
You know what, I'm getting a Debel Charge for my moniker.
From Yuji of Zanard.
You're a pro!
I've received a debel charge for voice camo!
Well, well, well, well... so let's get back to it.
And now, some more goods!
First of all, I introduced these to you all.
This is the first one, right?
Sakosh and...
Not "sakotsu"!
Tote bags.
So many tote bags.
Tote bags and...
This hat was modeled after that one, right?
Mugs.
Here's a mug.
Pouch.
Here it is. This is it.
It's a picture, isn't it?
It's a poster.
And the Daisen Rock Festival.
And this T-shirt, too.
Why don't we all wear them next year?
Let's really do something under the mountain!
Talk and eat.
Sounds fun!
Wow!
Well, well, well... here we are... as merchandise.
Please come to the Daikin Debel
TVK Mall
You can't buy them locally!
Made to order
That's right.
And one more thing.
Here's another one.
What is it, an acrylic stand?
Acrylic stand
Total 12 kinds
Amazing!
And the thing that made me laugh was...
You know what I think about acrylic stands?
I've heard from a lot of people wondering why they are so important...
But on New Year's Day...
I went there, and my Meiko and Oikko...
They bought it.
Of course they did.
I'm really popular with my kids.
I'll buy it.
So...
Well, they're in all kinds of poses.
Interesting poses, guys.
Interesting poses.
That's right.
Which one's the dumpling bun? Hey, which one is the dumpling bun?
Dumpling bread. Maybe this one.
This one.
I took the last one.
There's no sense of variation.
They're all in funny poses.
They're all the same.
That's the way it's supposed to be.
It's the royal way.
I posed in a classic pose.
This pose is too delicious.
Delicious!
What the hell is that?
It's delicious.
Yes, yes, yes.
There it is.
And...
Phone tabs & straps
Straps.
Strap
That's it, isn't it?
You put it between the phone and the case.
You can put it between the phone and the case
You can put it between the phone and the case.
when you hang it up.
It's called a phone tab.
There is a front and a back.
The front is a picture
but the back side is a picture of a creature
the picture of a living creature.
It's nice.
It brings back memories... the legendary creatures.
There's a lot of them.
And the Sarpon, they're very heavy.
It's an original.
I like the originals, too.
I'm a creature myself. I'm a creature of one too.
Can I ask you to draw it?
Don't tell me it's only living things. I'm a human being.
I'm out of the closet every time. I'm out of the closet.
I'd like to have one of these, too.
I hope you'll all take this opportunity to stop by and take a look.
But, you know, for this price, there are 12 different kinds of products... and you can buy them all at once.
Fontaboo and straps... you have to buy it... you have to buy it... you have to buy it...
Yay!
I'll use it!
I'll use it.
How's it going with the live audience?
Some of you are saying, "Let's win!
Oh, yes...
We had a BFF at the Taikan Grand Devil, right?
We had a BFF once, and each of us formed a unit.
What was amazing was that...
Gyoza and Kunitachi formed a unit with Kobayashi Kaho and Ukulele Revolution.
Revolution was much better.
I sang almost like a soloist.
I sang almost like a solo singer, and the National Unity danced and danced around me.
They went around like this all the time.
It was a true ukulele revolution!
I was able to perform as Revolution.
And there were a lot of guys from Tokyo, including me.
So we formed a group called Tokyo Metropolitans.
We sing songs about Tokyo.
And Hoshina and I would go down the aisle and say, "They're not gyaru, they're gyaru.
I like "gal gals".
They're not gals.
We're thinking of some special combinations this time, too.
We're thinking of some special combinations.
I think it'll be interesting to see them all together.
Yes, I think it would be interesting if we could get them all to work together.
Yes, the number of young people has increased.
The young people, the young people, the young people...
What kind of organization is this? What kind of organization is this?
It's a group of people.
So, please, please, please, please, please, please, please...
We'd appreciate it if you'd send a letter to the program.
Yes, I think so.
I think so, please.
That's all I have to say.
Well, I guess that's it for today's live broadcast.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
We've received a lot of devil's charges.
We're celebrating with a twist of mimicry and a personal commentary
Yasuke-san gave it to us
Thank you very much!
And Mr. Nagaoka got a front row seat at the Devils' Grandstand!
He's at the very front!
I don't know what to say...
Well, you know, it's only for those who want to go.
We don't know each other's faces.
I know his name.
Nagaoka, for example, often sends us his name.
Of course I know his name.
But I don't know his face.
They put a nametag on me.
I think they all do.
I think they'll make one for me.
I want you to wear it.
They might say, "Oh, you're Nagaoka.
You're Nagaoka?
Or more specifically, "You're m-Nagaoka?
Nagaoka.
And so on.
Like that...
That's all right.
If you don't want to be found out, that's fine.
Well, that's the way it is.
See you next week, right?
That's right. Right.
I'll see you next week.
Well, next week again at 8:00 a.m.?
At 8:00.
Next week at 8:00, you'll have to watch the live feed.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
See you next week.
Bye, bye, bye.